musiceternal.com 2016-11-06

# Privacy-Policy: Privacy-Policy

**Membership Information**

All information provided by either a music label, musical artist, DJ, RJ, music distributor, and/or partner is only for the development of profiles on Music Eternal and for content of such entities on Music Eternal for promotional purposes only. This material is never used to present these entities in a negative light, to provide disinformation, and/or provide information of a personal nature. Any information considered personal in nature is only at the consent of the entity in question prior to any posting on Music Eternal.

Promotional material is presented as new content, reviews, or presenting material of a written, audio, or visual nature of entities in such material. Material that is provided by these entities is still in the ownership of such entities and is disclosed at the bottom of each page in the Copyright section of each respective page.

**What information do we collect?**

Information is gathered through three resources.

**1)   Servers**

Our servers gather location, IP Addresses, pages visited, and duration of visit. This information is stored in secure logs within our servers. IP Addresses are never replicated outside of these logs. Demographic information and page visits are only used for marketing purposes. These are gathered based on overall numbers, never based on specific visits.

**2) E-Mails**

Mailing services in the shape of a Music Eternal newsletters will accept e-mails once accivated. This information will be stored within the servers only in an encrypted fashion. All work pertaining to e-mailing will be fully automated to ensure that no person will have access to such e-mails.

**3) Advertisers**

 Each advertiser will be a third-party that places advertisements through javascript on Music Eternal. These advertisers may gather information of visitors using their own methods that may include the use of cookies. This information is used solely for the prupose of providing ads that are more catered to visitors of Music Eternal. If there is cause for concern regarding these advertisements or questions regarding the advertisements placed on Music Eternal, please contact us at [ clientservices@musiceternal.com](mailto:clientservices@musiceternal.com). 

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy..

 **What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

1) To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

2) To send periodic emails

> The email address you provide may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to Music Eternal news and updates.

 **Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

 **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

 **Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

 **California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

 **Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

 **Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

 **Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our [privacy policy](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/).

 **Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

PO Box 540146  
North Salt Lake, Utah 84054  
United States  
clientservices@musiceternal.com  
8017979799
